Manikanta Koppala

FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER

Having 6 years of experience in front end web development, I am always passionate about design and development combination. The front end is something I admire every day and try to learn something new every time.

I love learning. I always spend time reading or learning a new skill (Piano IIII is something exciting me nowadays)

Work Experience

SDE - III Jan 2021 - Present

Livspace

- Promoted to lead the team of 7 members.
- Responsible for driving the team in terms of tech and product delivery.
- Worked on building Mirco Front-end Applications
- Initiated the process for unit testing & stream lined in our application and build process

SDE-II Dec 2018 - Jan 2021

Zeta (Direct I)

- Won outstanding performer award for two consecutive years
- Mentoring and guiding my co-workers
- Responsible for front end progress among my team
- Initiated & Developed <u>VUE plugin based development</u> architecture

Web Developer/Designer

Apr 2016 - Dec 2018

Agile Labs Pvt Ltd

- Promoted to evaluate the code(code review)
- Mentoring others in writing the code in a better way
- Manage to distribute the work every day
- Leading the team in the development process
- Earned to have a close discussion with management in the matter of application development.

Education

ONLINE 2016 - ∞

My love of learning never ends. I am gaining an incredible knowledge every day from places like Udemy, Coursera, FrontEnd masters and many more.

Bachelor Degree in Electronics & Communication

2011 - 2015

manikanta.koppala7@gmail.com

(+91) 9177703477

Bangalore, India 💡

mani-koppala.web.app



Skills

ES6 JavaScript

Vue JS Micro Frontend

JEST JS Design Patterns

Node JS PHP

HTML & CSS React Js

SCSS ML

AWS ++ many more

PROJECTS

Besides work, I love to build some projects for fun in my free time, which enhances my skills and be up to date with the trend. Like,

Telegram Bots **AWS**

Firebase Open Source API

Flutter Apps

Competencies

Team work | Love Of Learning | Appreciation of Beauty | Emotional Intelligence | Management | Time management

Interests & Hobbies

UI/UX | Fitness | Meditation | Reading | Tidying | Video Games | Blogger

SIR C.R.REDDY COE

CGPA: 7.39/10